

# ALEXANDRU COMANESCU

## **About Me**

I am a cybersecurity enthusiast dedicated to expanding my skill set. I am actively engaged in continuous learning, pursuing expertise in both offensive and defensive cybersecurity, particularly in Penetration Testing and Red Team. I am highly qualified for any type of job since I am self-taught in most of my learning and I learn very fast.

- C
- +32 471 52 77 91
- alex.coman.be@gmail.com
- <u>LinkedIn alex-coman-kr31tos</u>
- 0
- Ghent Metropolitan Area, Belgium

#### Language

- English (Good)
- Spanish (native)
- Romanian (native)

#### Skills Summary

- Responsible and professional
- Vulnerability Analysis
- Network Security
- Security Policies and Procedures
- Security Tools and Technologies
- Adaptability
- Web Application Testing
- Punctual
- Cheerful and motivated

### Experience

## AGP eGlass Soliver (2024)

**WST OPERATOR** 

-Responsible for the use of robots that manufacture windows for different car models, adding appropriate values for correct manufacturing as well as maintenance of these robots for optimal performance.

## ADIENT SL (2021-2024)

PRODUCT QUALITY INSPECTOR

- -Perform rigorous quality testing, including performance testing, durability testing and safety testing, to validate the integrity and reliability of our products.
- -Conduct thorough inspections throughout the manufacturing process to identify potential quality deviations and take proactive corrective action.

# **COPISTERIA LOW COST (2018-2021)**

WEB TASK MANAGER

- -Management of print quality and online customer service. Monitor customer orders and manage staff to carry out the order correctly.
- -A position of responsibility that included deciding on printing formats, printer configuration and printer repair.

#### Education

## **KEEPCODING (2023-2024)**

**Bootcamp Full Stack Cybersecurity** 

At this well-known Bootcamp based in Sillicon Valley I am learning the basics of cybersecurity as Purple Team. I'll have it finished in July 2024.

## HACK4U (2023)

**Cybersecurity Academy** 

In this Academy I learned Linux, Scripting with Python and an introduction to Hacking

# ACADEMIA X (2023)

**Bootcamp Full Stack Software Developer** 

In this Academy I learned HTML, CSS, JavaScript and an introduction to SQL.

## **BACHELOR OF HUMANITIES (2016-2018)**

Baccalaureate in social sciences